Guide to the Records of American Association for Ethiopian Jews (AAEJ), undated, 1960-1961, 1963, 1965-1968, 1970-1995, 2001-2002 *I-503
American Jewish Historical Society, Boston, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup II: AAEJ Activists, undated, 1961, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1970-1993; Boxes 38-139.
  - Series A: LaDena Schnapper (AAEJ Coordinator) Files, undated, 1961, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1970-1991; Boxes 38-120.
    - Subseries 2: Schnapper Rescue and Relief, undated, 1968, 1970-1991; Boxes 42-89.
      - Subsubseries a: Rescue and Relief A-Z, undated, 1970-1991; Boxes 42-65.
        - Zion Seyoum family, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 32)
      - Subsubseries b: Rescue/Relief Ethiopians to Israel, undated, 1970-1990; Boxes 66-83.
        The subsubseries contains the rescue and relief files collected by Schnapper of the Ethiopian Jews fleeing to Israel from 1970 to 1990. The files arranged alphabetically by first name and often contain correspondence in Amharic as well as Yiddish. The files often contain correspondence from LaDena Schnapper to the Falashas asking for more information in order to assist with the completion of the case work files. The records themselves are an accurate reflection of the situation faced by the Ethiopian Jews and are a valuable source of information to researchers interested in the rescue and relief effort of the Ethiopian Jews.
        - Abebe Berhan (Uri Ben Yair) (contains photographs), undated, 1985-1990 (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - Abebe Solomon, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - Abechew Meharie, undated, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 3)
        - Abere Dessalegne, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - Aberham-Melaku (contains photograph), 1987 (Box 66, Folder 5)
        - Aberhame Mehary, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 6)
        - Abibit Tizazu, undated, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 7)
        - Abraham Askias, 1986-1988 (Box 66, Folder 8)
        - Abraham Asres, 1986-1989 (Box 66, Folder 9)
        - Abraham Beyene Neguise, 1986-1990 (Box 66, Folder 10)
        - Abraham Dejene, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 11)
        - Abraham Miheret Eskias, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 12)
        - Abraham Negussie, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 13)
        - Abraham Sahilu, 1983-1984, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 14)
        - Abreha Miheret Askias, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 15)
        - Achamyeleh Gebeyehu, undated, 1972, 1974, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 66, Folder 16)
        - Acheshe Tekelu (Mary Yigzaw mother), 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 17)
        - Adane Worku, 1983-1985 (Box 66, Folder 18)
        - Adane Zeghaye, 1986-1987 (Box 66, Folder 19)
        - Adanech Yosef (empty folder) (Box 66, Folder 20)
        - Addisie Simon, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 21)
        - Addisu Dawit, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 22)
        - Addisu Mehari Dinku, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 23)
        - Addisu Messele, 1986-1989 (Box 66, Folder 24)
        - Addisu Robel, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 25)
        - Addisu Sahlu, Aster Yemanu, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 66, Folder 26)
        - Addisu Selam, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 27)
        - Addisu Takele, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 28)
        - Addisu Yenewodage Tamino, undated, 1986-1990 (Box 67, Folder 1)
        - Adebaray Melkiass, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 2)
        - Adeneh Birhanu, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 3)
        - Adeneku Mehari, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 67, Folder 4)
        - Aderajew Robel, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 67, Folder 5)
        - Adey Takale, undated, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 6)
        - Adina Negussie, 1988-1990 (Box 67, Folder 7)
        - Admase Menasie, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 8)
        - Admase Muchneh, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 9)
        - Adna Mola, 1987, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 10)
        - Aerihly Melaku, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 11)
        - Aineshete Gete, undated, 1983-1986 (Box 67, Folder 12)
        - Akalu Fisseha, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 67, Folder 13)
        - Aklilu Berhan, 1983, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 14)
        - Aklilu Yehewlashet, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 15)
        - Aklum Ferede, 1982, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 16)
        - Alemadis Getu, undated, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 17)
        - Alemata Sahale, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 18)
        - Alemnew Awarke Getahun, undated, 1984-1987 (Box 67, Folder 19)
        - Alemnew Aworku, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 20)
        - Alemsahi Tiku, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 67, Folder 21)
        - Alemu Ambaw, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 22)
        - Alemu Belay, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 23)
        - Alemu Esheti, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 24)
        - Alemu Eshetie, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 25)
        - Alemu Tarekegn, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 26)
        - Alene Melesse (empty folder) (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - Ali Yahu Yacob, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - Alimitu Ferede, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - Alimitu Muche, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - Alitaw Esayas, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 5)
        - Allefu Wubie, 1986-1989 (Box 68, Folder 6)
        - Almaz - Shiferaw, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 7)
        - Almaz Tekeste, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 68, Folder 8)
        - Alon Yesmes, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 9)
        - Amanuel Zewdie, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 10)
        - Amare Belay, 1985, 1988, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 11)
        - Ambachew Mola, 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 12)
        - Ambechew Simane, 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 13)
        - Andualem Enyew Berhane (empty folder) (Box 68, Folder 14)
        - Aneyesh Berihun, undated, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 15)
        - Aragie - Takele, undated, 1987-1990 (Box 68, Folder 16)
        - Arega Tadesse, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 17)
        - Arez Kindie, 1987-1989 (Box 68, Folder 18)
        - Asef Asrese, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 19)
        - Asegedetch Eshete, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 20)
        - Aselef Telele, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 21)
        - Asemamaw Berhanu, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 22)
        - Aserebeb Alemu, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 23)
        - Asfaw Chole, undated, 1983-1985, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 24)
        - Asfaw Fente, undated, 1984-1990 (Box 68, Folder 25)
        - Asfaw Zeru, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 26)
        - Askabu Estubdink, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 27)
        - Asmamaw Mengistu, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 28)
        - Asmar Ngashe, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 29)
        - Asmara Bantihun (Schmuel Alama), 1987 (Box 68, Folder 30)
        - Asmara Mamuye, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 31)
        - Asmaratch Tezaza, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 32)
        - Asmare Eshetie (Shem-tov Zemzu), 1990 (Box 68, Folder 33)
        - Asmaru Mamuye, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 34)
        - Asmaru Tefere, 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 35)
        - Asmaru Tarekegne, 1987-1990 (Box 68, Folder 36)
        - Asnakew Sendeke, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - Asnakew Worku Family, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - Asnakew Worku, undated, 1976, 1985, 1987-1989 (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Asressie Negatu, 1986-1988 (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Assayde Blechay, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Assefa Abeba, 1987, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Assefa Belay, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - Assefa Bogale, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - Assefa Gete (Yoseph Zvadia), 1985 (Box 69, Folder 9)
        - Assefa Mengesha (contains photograph), undated, 1978, 1986-1990 (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Asself Shetu, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - Assemar Belaye, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 12)
        - Assof Fered, 1984-1989 (Box 69, Folder 13)
        - Atalay Tedla, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 14)
        - Atanaw Yigelegne, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 15)
        - Atkaw Tefere, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 16)
        - Averham Yitzchak, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 17)
        - Aviva Eleazar, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 18)
        - Avraham Yitzchak, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 19)
        - Ayalew Asefa, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 20)
        - Ayanaw Demewozie, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 69, Folder 21)
        - Ayanaw Desalegne, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 22)
        - Ayanaw Hailu, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 23)
        - Ayanaw Meharie, undated, 1985-1987 (Box 69, Folder 24)
        - Ayanaw Selam, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 25)
        - Ayanew Nega, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 26)
        - Ayanow Belay, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 27)
        - Ayneshet Esaysas, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 28)
        - Azalech Etsubdink, undated, 1987-1990 (Box 69, Folder 29)
        - Azezew Bitewulgne, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 30)
        - Azzeb Dessalegn, 1986-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - Barhue Eyob, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 2)
        - Barkew - Yalew, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 3)
        - Baruch Amlak Teka (empty folder) (Box 70, Folder 4)
        - Baruch Chekole, undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
        - Baruch Ferdu, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 6)
        - Baruch Gete, undated, 1979, 1984-1990 (Box 70, Folder 7)
        - Baruch Shmuel, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - Baruch Tarkin, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 9)
        - Baruch Tegegne, 1980, 1982-1983, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 10)
        - Baruch Tegegne Report, Jan-86 (Box 70, Folder 11)
        - Baruch Yacov, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 12)
        - Baruch - Yehuda, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 13)
        - Baruch Zewde, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 14)
        - Baruk Yacob Belay, 1984-1990 (Box 70, Folder 15)
        - Batya Ysayas, 1989-1990 (Box 70, Folder 16)
        - Baye Fisseha, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 17)
        - Bayleyegne Mengistie (contains photographs), undated, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 18)
        - Bayouh Terefe Mehari, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 19)
        - Bayouh Terrefe, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 20)
        - Bayuh Mehari, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 21)
        - Bazetu Mulu Birha Alube, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 22)
        - Belay Malku, undated (Box 70, Folder 23)
        - Benny Sahalu, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 24)
        - Berhanu Akale, undated, 1984-1989 (Box 70, Folder 25)
        - Berhanu Mehari (contains photograph), 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 26)
        - Berhanu Robel (contains photographs), undated, 1973, 1984-1986, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 27)
        - Berhana Semone (contains photographs), undated, 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 28)
        - Berke Lemma, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 29)
        - Bewket Mihretu, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 30)
        - Bewketu Wubie, 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 31)
        - Bezunesh Alazar, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 32)
        - Bimerew Demewizie, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 33)
        - Bimeru Tafeta, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 34)
        - Birku Kehateh, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 35)
        - Birle Malaku, undated, 1974, 1983-1989 (Box 70, Folder 36)
        - Bitewligne Tayachew, 1988-1990 (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - Bitewulgne Haim, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - Bono Bayo Yishake, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 3)
        - Bosena Awoke, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - Bosena Fentahun, undated, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 5)
        - Bosena Malaku, 1987, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 6)
        - Buta Assemerine, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 7)
        - Chaim Negist, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 8)
        - Chale Getahun, undated, 1985-1987 (Box 71, Folder 9)
        - Chana Melaku, 1987, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 10)
        - Chane Admasu, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 11)
        - Chane Kebret, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 12)
        - Chole Tftie, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 13)
        - Daite Yaakov, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 14)
        - Dani Yasmain (contains photograph), undated, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 15)
        - Daniel Jonass, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 16)
        - Daniel Meshesha (contains photograph), 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 17)
        - Daniel Rata, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 18)
        - Daniel Seyoum, 1985-1987 (Box 71, Folder 19)
        - David Girmaie, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 20)
        - David Golla, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 21)
        - David Seyoum, 1982, 1985-1990 (Box 71, Folder 22)
        - David Tessema, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 71, Folder 23)
        - David Tizazu, 1989-1990 (Box 71, Folder 24)
        - David Zaudu, 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 25)
        - Dawit Abrham, 1989-1990 (Box 71, Folder 26)
        - Dejene Reta, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 27)
        - Demilew Reddie, 1987-1990 (Box 71, Folder 28)
        - Derebe Alemayehu, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 29)
        - Derege Negussie, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 30)
        - Dereje Arefaine, 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 31)
        - Derso Jegne, 1989-1990 (Box 71, Folder 32)
        - Dessalegn Solomon, 1984-1987 (Box 71, Folder 33)
        - Dessalegn Terekegne, undated, 1983-1988 (Box 71, Folder 34)
        - Desse Tukuye, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 35)
        - Desta Makonnen, 1987-1990 (Box 71, Folder 36)
        - Desta Mengistu, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 37)
        - Dror Sebho, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 38)
        - Edna Alelegne, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 39)
        - Edna Mehari (contains photographs), undated, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 40)
        - Elan Melesse, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 41)
        - Elani Negat (Bosena Ameha), undated, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 42)
        - Eli Melech Tedela, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 43)
        - Eli (Genetu) Mengistu, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 44)
        - Elias Baruch, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 71, Folder 45)
        - Elimelech Terunach, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 1)
        - Elimlhe Tedela, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 2)
        - Elizabeth Fentu, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 3)
        - Emmanual Zewdu (contains photograph), 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 4)
        - Enatmar Selam (empty folder) (Box 72, Folder 5)
        - Enatmar Teruneh, 1983-1988 (Box 72, Folder 6)
        - Endalem Enayaw, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 7)
        - Endalew Tilahun, 1988-1989 (Box 72, Folder 8)
        - Enenu Shifaro, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 9)
        - Eneyew Bogale, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 10)
        - Eniyish Meteku Denku, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 11)
        - Ephraim Yonan (empty folder) (Box 72, Folder 12)
        - Esayus (Yeshayahu) Chane, 1982-1983, 1986-1989 (Box 72, Folder 13)
        - Eshet Getenet, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 14)
        - Esheta Berehun, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 15)
        - Eshete Ferede, undated, 1986-1990 (Box 72, Folder 16)
        - Eshetu Fiseha, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 17)
        - Eshetu Zemene, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 18)
        - Ester Hollender, 1985-1987 (Box 72, Folder 19)
        - Ester Kassay, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 20)
        - Ester Mitiku, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 21)
        - Esther Dinku, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 22)
        - Etenesh Melesse (Eshete Ferede's mother), 1988-1989 (Box 72, Folder 23)
        - Etsa Genet Amare, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 24)
        - Etye Meharie, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 25)
        - Eyayu Berhanu, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 26)
        - Dr. Eyilachew Trunh, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 27)
        - Eyob Yehulashet, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 28)
        - Ezezaw Ayichew, 1987-1990 (Box 72, Folder 29)
        - Ezra Tezago, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 30)
        - Fasil Legesse, 1986-1990 (Box 72, Folder 31)
        - Fekede & Mula Assefa, undated, 1987-1990 (Box 72, Folder 32)
        - Fenta Getachew, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 33)
        - Fentahun Degif Molla, 1988-1990 (Box 72, Folder 34)
        - Fentayh Abera, undated, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 1)
        - Fentanesh Tefete, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 2)
        - Fentie Abraham Yayeh, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 3)
        - Ferede Tesfai, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 4)
        - Fetegu (Nudew Molla), 1987-1988 (Box 73, Folder 5)
        - Fetelework Dargie, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
        - Gad Aletaw, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 7)
        - Gadie Eshetu, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 8)
        - Gedelia Uriya (Uri Ben Gad), 1981, 1984-1987, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 9)
        - Getachew Demissie (Senaite Mequanitie), undated, 1985-1990 (Box 73, Folder 10)
        - Getachew Gusha, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 11)
        - Getaneh Bogale, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 12)
        - Gethe Tewodros, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 13)
        - Gideon Lemma Bitwelign, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 14)
        - Gideon Masala, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 15)
        - Giela Kebade, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 16)
        - Giora Mequant, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 17)
        - Girmay Sebhat, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 18)
        - Gobeze Tsegahun, Senat Truneh, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 19)
        - Gobezie Achenefe, 1988-1990 (Box 73, Folder 20)
        - Godi Shati, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 21)
        - Guade Worku, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 22)
        - Hagit Mekonnen, 1987, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 23)
        - Hagit Simon, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 24)
        - Hailu Melisse (contains photographs), 1975, 1985-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 25)
        - Hailu Mihiret, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 26)
        - Haim Tiruneh (empty folder) (Box 73, Folder 27)
        - Hana Sahlu, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 28)
        - Hana Yishak, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 29)
        - Hazi Ovadia, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 30)
        - Hirut Tekle, undated, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 73, Folder 31)
        - Israel Beyene, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 32)
        - Israel Hailu, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 33)
        - Israel Itzhak, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 34)
        - Itshak Yosef, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 35)
        - Jonatan Asnakewe, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 36)
        - Josef Dawit, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 73, Folder 37)
        - Judith Feleke (Yiragadu Gette), 1988 (Box 73, Folder 38)
        - Kafalo Mekonen, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 39)
        - Kassa Ferede, undated, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 40)
        - Kassaye Tizazu, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 41)
        - Kebedetch Wodage, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 42)
        - Kebie Fredu, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 43)
        - Kegnuzmach Reta, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 44)
        - Kibeb Mamo, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 1)
        - Kibeb Mamo, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 2)
        - Kibretia Gessese, 1986-1988 (Box 74, Folder 3)
        - Kidanu Tewebe, 1987-1990 (Box 74, Folder 4)
        - Kifle Tessema, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 5)
        - Koke Gete, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 6)
        - Lakech Kassa Yehulashet, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 7)
        - Laketch Tadesse, 1986-1988 (Box 74, Folder 8)
        - Lakia Sisay, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 9)
        - Leha Tamno, 1987, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 10)
        - Lelt Gebrie, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 74, Folder 11)
        - Lemlem Minewab, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 12)
        - Lemma Bayeh (Israel?) (Rescue), 1990 (Box 74, Folder 13)
        - Letay Gebre Medin (empty folder) (Box 74, Folder 14)
        - Letay Geremedin, undated, 1985-1988 (Box 74, Folder 15)
        - Leulseged Negussie, 1986-1987 (Box 74, Folder 16)
        - Leulseged Tulu, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 74, Folder 17)
        - Lewtie Demissie, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 18)
        - Machon Meir, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 19)
        - Mahratu Zarihun, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 74, Folder 20)
        - Maloha Samuel, undated, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 21)
        - Malka Melesse, 1986-1987 (Box 74, Folder 22)
        - Mamay Solomon, 1986-1987 (Box 74, Folder 23)
        - Mamo Alef, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 24)
        - Mamo Alef family, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 25)
        - Mamo Mola, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 26)
        - Manalabash Mola, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 27)
        - Manalash Yishak, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 28)
        - Mandefro Wubie, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 29)
        - Mare Mekonnet, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 30)
        - Mare Yigzaw (contains photographs), undated, 1977, 1985-1990 (Box 74, Folder 31)
        - Marelegn Messfine, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 32)
        - Marta Worku, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 33)
        - Maru Taniru, 1987-1990 (Box 74, Folder 34)
        - Maru Zellele, undated, 1984-1988, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 35)
        - Mayir Zari, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 1)
        - Mebrat Birhanu, 1988-1989 (Box 75, Folder 2)
        - Mehari Assefa, 1987-1990 (Box 75, Folder 3)
        - Mehari Deg, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 4)
        - Mehari Minuwab, 1986-1990 (Box 75, Folder 5)
        - Mehari Robel, undated, 1971, 1973, 1976, 1979, 1982, 1984-1990 (Box 75, Folder 6)
        - Mehari Tikuya, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 7)
        - Mengiste Kebede, 1985-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 8)
        - Meheretu Zerihun, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 75, Folder 9)
        - Meir Makonnen Zerie, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 10)
        - Mekonan Sibhat, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 75, Folder 11)
        - Mekonen Melesse, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 12)
        - Mekuria Engdaw, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 13)
        - Mekuria Yemeharen, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 14)
        - Melaku Lakia, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 15)
        - Melkam Meherete, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 16)
        - Melke Asres, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 17)
        - Menachem Meheret (empty folder) (Box 75, Folder 18)
        - Mengiste Tezazu, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 75, Folder 19)
        - Mengiste Tizazu, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 20)
        - Mengistu Abraham, undated, 1976, 1986-1989 (Box 75, Folder 21)
        - Mengistu Abraham, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 75, Folder 22)
        - Mengistu Solomon, 1984-1986 (Box 76, Folder 1)
        - Mengistu Yishak, undated, 1985-1990 (Box 76, Folder 2)
        - Mentosonit Solomon, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 3)
        - (Mesele) Kinde Chole, undated, 1977, 1984-1990 (Box 76, Folder 4)
        - Mesfin Ambau, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 5)
        - Mesfin Ayechew, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 6)
        - Mesfin Chekol, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 7)
        - Mesfin Kebede, 1989-1990 (Box 76, Folder 8)
        - Mesfin Melaku, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 9)
        - Meskeram Shibru, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 10)
        - Mesresha Chayim Batauli, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 11)
        - Metekia Berhanu, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 76, Folder 12)
        - Mequanent Rede, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 13)
        - Mexesa Pinhas, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 14)
        - Michael Tessema, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 15)
        - Miheret Sebehat, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 16)
        - Mimi Na'im (empty folder) (Box 76, Folder 17)
        - Mintwab Motbaynir, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 18)
        - Misanesh Mehari, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 19)
        - Mogus Atanaw, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 76, Folder 20)
        - Mogus Mehretu (contains photograph), undated, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 21)
        - Mogus Yesak Mekeru, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 22)
        - Mola Chane, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 76, Folder 23)
        - Mola Nadew, 1987-1989 (Box 76, Folder 24)
        - Moshe Baruch, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 25)
        - Moshe (Demozie) Baruk, undated, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 1)
        - Moshe Mengistu, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 2)
        - Moshe Seyum, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 3)
        - Motbaynor Desta, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Muchet Abera, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Mulatu Dessie, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 6)
        - Mulu Aberra, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 7)
        - Mulu Alemu, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 8)
        - Mulu Astatkew, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 9)
        - Mulu Sahilu Elias, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 10)
        - Mulu Teshome, 1989-1990 (Box 77, Folder 11)
        - Mulualem Tarekegn, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 12)
        - Mulugeta Moges, 1986-1990 (Box 77, Folder 13)
        - Mulukan Fanta, 1988-1989 (Box 77, Folder 14)
        - Muluken Fenta, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 15)
        - Muluwork and Fassel Adamsu, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 16)
        - Myra Mamou, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 17)
        - Naomi Shmuel, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 18)
        - Natan Makuria, 1987-1988 (Box 77, Folder 19)
        - Natanael Tezazre (Eyeyew Berhan), 1985-1988 (Box 77, Folder 20)
        - Nega Berhanu, 1986-1989 (Box 77, Folder 21)
        - Nega (Kebede) Ishetie, 1985-1987 (Box 77, Folder 22)
        - Negest Ashakew, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 23)
        - Negusa Rama, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 24)
        - Negussie Asfaw, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 25)
        - Negusie Ayelegne and Tewba Asefa, 1981, 1984-1985, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 26)
        - Negussie Ayelegne, 1988-1989 (Box 77, Folder 27)
        - Noan Asras, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 28)
        - Ora Chekole, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 29)
        - Oshrat Tedela, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 30)
        - Phina Selemon, 1987, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 31)
        - Pinchas Malasa, undated, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 32)